Friends, if you have Ola or Ola's S1 Pro
and you have bought it in 2022, then
you must have been reminded that your
insurance is about to expire, it must have expired
here, where it is about to expire,
so today in this video we will
talk about the same, at the time when you
bought the scooter, then Ola company must have given you
insurance from ICICI Lombard company, in which there is
a care ODI match cover
and 5 years of third party coverage
was included together, so your own damage is covered
and third party's coverage is also covered,
if you are not doing your new, then it
cannot stop you from running, you still have four years of
third party
insurance, but if you suffer your own loss, then
that will not be covered, you will have to spend
money on it yourself, so it's better that you pay the
premium and insure your scooter,
if there is a financial problem, then you
can also leave the third party insurance and
if you do not spend much money with it, then
you can also take a comprehensive plan,
I am going to cover these three-four things today in the
video  So stay tuned till the end of the video
and hit the subscribe button on the channel. If you are
new then I also got a message from
ICICI Lombard that the
insurance of your scooter is about to expire,
so if you want to get your own damage
cover then you
can get it by paying a premium, so the premium is approximately around Rs.
I will show you that
message also and if you are thinking
that you can get insurance from Policy Bazaar, then
I will also show you how you
can do it, which insurance companies are
providing you options in January 2030,
so I also wanted to save some money and see
which options are available, so we
turned to Policy Bazaar, we went to Policy Bazaar
and after that as you know
that you have to type your number,
scooter, bike or car, so we
typed the number of our scooter, after that
we will get options which companies are
providing us insurance,
after this they search your details, so
first you have to type your  You have to do a city heart attack
like I did mine, you can do it,
after that you have to tell your company
which brand your two wheeler is, so
we selected Ola here, Ola's S Van model, if there was
no option after S Van then you do not need a photo etc.,
if there is one then you will have to do it,
after this you were asked
which insurance OnePlus 5T was, so we
selected the option of OnePlus 5 here, so
friends, right now we are getting insurance of only Bajaj Allianz company
whose ID is also
showing
80000795, so there is only one insurance company which is
giving it right now, no
other company is listed here,
if you want to get it done from any other company, you can get it done from the offline market,
we
tried to change the ID here also but the ID was
not changing, the maximum was
not changing and it was not getting customized also,
so if you
want to get your S1 done on this amount then you
can get it done, if you want to
pay less insurance premium then you can get it done from third party,
you have it  So after this we went to
insurance. Many people had taken it when they
bought a new scooter, so we also thought of
trying it. We are trying it now, so
going here also we have to select our bike,
which is the model, so here
we typed Ola's option, here the
Ola S18.5 kilo watt
C, has it expired or not, so
we said it has not expired, it is still running, so
they showed us the comprehensive plan,
comprehensive plan means
that you will have to pay a little bigger expense, including
file charges, so it is
showing Rs 2040 plus GST, if you
take one year and two years in January 2023, then a
little discount is also given along with it,
if there are only third party people then
you will have to pay this much money, we have 1161 third
party, so we do not need it,
now you will ask something else that the third party
can be different and it can be difficult to find,
I will answer this also, so that comprehensive plan
told what will be covered, accident,
fire
Calamity loss and personal accidental cover will
cover everything. But in this, as it happens, when
our vehicle gets old, then
after that we have to invest money ourselves, for
parts like plastic
kits, so it means nothing will happen without paying,
you will have to
pay some money from your side, so we did not
take Ko and there is no benefit from Bajaj, so for the
policy that was available in the market, we
feel that we will have to go to ICICI Lombard for the
time being,
I am talking to you about 200 of January 2030, it is
possible that in the future some more
companies will list their policies in the market, right now
these are electric scooters, so it is difficult
because not many companies have come to sell
electric scooters, God willing, now
we talk about when
we are going to take insurance, can we
take third party insurance from any other company, so yes friends, you
can take it, there is no problem in this,
third party insurance comes when
someone gets harmed due to your scooter
and that FIR is filed and a case is filed against you,  It
will decide how much money you have to pay to the
third party. It does not happen like this, so if
in real life there is some damage to the scooter, then the
on-damage insurance company will
give you the money, the third party
comes into your account only when your insurance becomes legal.
Right now the thing is that if you take it from us,
which is ICC Lombard, then there is a
comprehensive option in it and there is also a dub
cap option, so right now it will cover the parts of the scooter, so you should
not compromise on a little premium, so
when there is any damage to the scooter, then that much
money will have to be paid from your pocket, so you should
take the complete package and if you want to
take insurance, then
take it before it expires because it happens that if
your insurance expires, then
your scooter will be photographed again
and if there is any scratch etc. then that
account gets tabled, when your photographs are taken then it is
visible there and later if there is
any damage etc. then they will
tell you in advance that there was
damage here before the insurance, so this will
not be included, so if your insurance post  It is going to be on the
10th, so you should
take new insurance by the 10th, so that
whatever old scratches, damages, broken panels etc. are there in your scooter,
you can get them replaced at any time.
Right now this scooter is expensive and fire
incidents also happen sometimes, so it is
mandatory to take both of these. It has a
good speed too, so even if we don't want to, if
we drive it in fast mode, then if
these scratches etc. come,
they get covered in the insurance policy. So
friend, from now on I will use the company only. I will take the
insurance which is of ICC,
along with that I will take the cover
which is called depression and personal extent cover as
well because for 4,500 rupees if you put your life
and your family's life at risk, then
that is of no use. You are
saving so much money on petrol, there is a
little bit, we spent on insurance for free, so it does not matter that much.
If you are going to some other company, do that. If you are going to
some other company offline,
then let us know in the comment box.
Please do tell us so that our ordinance
also gets some awareness.